[{"answer": "What do you mean, 'what is it?' It's a country right next to that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "And you're the shark", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know how a fish could eat laughs", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Whatever you get", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Don't tell me she's dragging another poor guy across that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Okay, alright listen. Forget about The Gap because we are through", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Fine", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I don't want you to think that anyone's gonna treat you any differently just because of your, uh, handicap", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm sorry. Differently, uh, advantaged", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Someone's cooking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hello, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm not the one doing the cooking, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No, he's up on the roof getting some sun with the butter", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah. my friend tries to read but cannot concentrate", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Tell me about it, I don't know why I ever took you back", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "That's it! I cannot take this! I mean, look at this, nothing has changed. We're back together two hours, we're having the same problems we had 12 hours ago", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Please! I took you back. You know it, I know it, vegetable lasagna here knows it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hey, hey! You dented my ride. my friend walks back to inspect the damage", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "How about I do you a favor upside your head", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, you had some good stuff. The cancer bit? It was edgy, it was not my sort of thing but some of those people out there, they really liked it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Butter-Shave.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Like that guy who yelled out", "qsentId": 22}]